Thank you for watching!
Ouch.
I hit something on the door.
Good morning.
I'm so sleepy.
Good morning
Good morning, sir.
Where shall we go today?
Today I'm going to Nagoya.
That's why I'm here.
There's a stamp called "Michodane" here.
I'm wearing a mask!
Pioli!
I want to take Pioli home!
What's that?
It's a challenge to carry Pioli home without it falling apart.
I heard there's something about that.
I see.
It's really cute.
I know it's supposed to be a tiny mask, but...
But not this big.
Okay, let's see which one is the real Pioli.
The correct answer is...
This one.
Is it gone?
Oh, no! It's there.
I found it. I found it.
I found it.
It's Peoria.
I'm so happy.
It's the season, isn't it?
It's the time of year to break up the peoria.
Did you break it?
Look.
There's Pioli.
You had peoli?You're here?
There's chocolate, too.
Chocolate and normal chocolates.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy!
A lemon!
I found it!
Lots to laugh about today!
Yay!
Dad, I'm sorry I opened it first.
I'm so happy.
I hope it's good.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's go to the fridge.
Yogurt.
I came to buy this.
Bon appétit!
I'm so scared!
I'm so peeled!
Bye bye!
It's a little early, but I got a lunch box!
It's a 3-year-old's chicken rice bento.
There are two kinds.
One is chicken wings and the other is this.
I heard a rumor that the chicken wings would be brought in later, so I went for this one.
so I chose this one.
Also, Julia is going to stay for the campaign.
I'm sure I will be able to eat something.
I decided on this one, bye-bye!
Bye bye.
Good morning.
I think it's the last of the tour.
Twice. Second one? Next final.
And today will be the 9th stop.
I feel like I'm in school.It's like being in school.
Something like a school?
I don't even hear the door or the atmosphere anymore.
I'll go there for you.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it, because it has the atmosphere of a peori.
Oh, there's something here.
Who's that?
Who is it?
I could already see it from the bottom of the screen.
Today, the members decided to give each other and the person next to us a haircut,
Pioli decided for me.
Braided braids.
What do you think?
Also, Julian's haircut is a little different from the usual and rare,
Please look forward to it.
See you later.
Hito-chan decided on today's hairstyle.
Doesn't this look a bit synthetic?
Look, it looks a bit CG in the back.
And this dress, I wore it on a tour before, right?
Where was it, Niigata?
I'm afraid you'll think I'm wearing the same thing all the time.
But one-piece dresses are so comfortable.
I'm hungry, so I'm going to have a meal.
There were tatami mats in the dressing room
I made myself at home.
After eating, I'd like to exercise properly.
I'll tell you that.
I'll probably sleep again anyway.
Thank you for your hard work.
I haven't even fixed my bangs yet.
But this is Aki-chan's hair selection.
So cute!
Rokke, rokke, rokke!
Oh, armpit, armpit room
Ama-nyan!Ama-nyan
Bento Soboro (Lunchbox Soboro)
I knew it!
I got miso soup with red miso
It's a two thirds frame
This is the room where Kunamigi slept
She was showing Neji's picture of Itchy
Yay!
Ta-da!
It's miso soup with red miso.
It smells good.
The catering lady was with us.
A teardrop-shaped ladle. It was pre-made for left-handed people,
I would like to drink it.
There is a cherry blossom bath in it. I can't see.
Hey, here it comes!
Hey, I wanted to do this.
I saw you at Tsukihara.
No, let's upload it.
I'll upload it.
Oh, it's started.
I'm done uploading.
Can each person challenge up to 5 pictures a day?
Because the other day, I got a yakiniku bento from a friend,
I was eating it.
Please give the prize to the staff members.
Hitoka Yakiniku?
I'm going too.
Yakiniku, yakiniku.
I only heard one the other day.
Yuriya got rallied too, so should I ask sooner?
How many? Today.
Five today.
Okay, I'll take two first.
What? That's great, Aki-chan.What? That's right, Aki-chan.
Then, we're done.
You want to pull it together?
The "pikan pikan".
Okay, I'll pull.
Ready?
Here it comes.
The previous winner.
Isn't it nice?
It's so cute, even the bento.
It's Jin-chan's yakiniku bento.
Ready.
Hazare.
Hazure.
Because sometimes no one wins.
You'll win, won't you?
Hazure.
Hazure
Aren't they all a Hazura?
I'm going to hit it now.
Poypoo!
Happened.
Hazare.
I'm going.
I'm getting a lot of hazzles.
Bingo!
There are so many winners?
Hazurae...
No, it's not.No, it's not.
What?
No.
You're kidding?
I got something.
Ahhh...
Oh, no.
Oops.
Two cards.
The last one hit.
Yay~ I won.
Yukiniku bento. Yay!
Where are you going to see it?
I don't mind if it's a send-off party.
A send-off party?
That's so cute. Seriously, it's so cute.
I want to eat sweets.
Let's eat Imokenpoi.
I want to eat.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat it for the first time.
Well, I'll do some advertising in the meantime.
Wow. Something like this.
Churia.
It's good.
Hello.
I've won a prize, so I'm going to advertise a cute memorial.
The cover photo is also very cute,
The cover photo is also very cute.
The songs are all cute.
The choreography of the chorus is also very cute.
Many people have danced to the song on TikTok,
The choreography is also very cute,
The dialogue parts are also cute.
The coupling song,
I don't think everyone has heard it yet,I don't think you guys have heard it yet,
That coupling song is great.
Terete Teten.
It's great.
Terete Teten is really good.
Also, you know,
Teleteeten.
And, "Tente" is good, too.
Tente is also very good.
Tente has an image of a mirror ball,
But we also have a song like this.
It's really good.
Is this enough?
All the songs are really great,
I hope everyone is looking forward to the release of this album.
I'm very happy to have met so many wonderful songs this time as well.
I'm looking forward to the lunches.
Please give Jurian two muscle bentos.
He said okay.
Really?
He said he can have one for Oharu-chan too,
Jurian?
Yes, that's right.
I'd love to have it twice.
She's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
Can we use them as stickers?
I'll put them on everyone.
Isn't it pretty cute?
You're disgusting.
Don't look at me.
What are you doing?
Smile, smile, smile.
It's pretty sticky.
Expensive camera.
Excuse me.My apologies.
Hiyori just came to visit me,
Are you okay? Meat.
Is it okay?
Are you okay?
Okay, bye.
Bye, baby.
If you make a pretty face, I'll get them to make you a meat label.
You have to make a pretty face.
Of course, you can take it right here.
Mr. Miki Naru.
Let's make a melt face!
Let's make a melting face.
Are we going to the same restaurant?
Julien, this is Doala,
Oh, yeah, that's right, we're going to the same restaurant.
Doala image.
I miss it.
Well, then...
Time for a treat!
We had mandarin oranges and strawberries before.
This time, it's a limited time signature muscat.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Actually, I haven't reached the employee muscat yet.
But you know, it tastes like an employee muscat, even though I didn't knit it.
Mmm!
It's bursting.
Shine Muscat.
Delicious!
It's a single pinch, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Just now.Earlier.
Calamine asked me which one to take.
She said, "I think I'll just have one shaft.
I said, "No, but I think I'll have a julienne.
That's what I said.
It's only for boobs.
I love Michijiku!
I love figs. Yay!
Did you eat a Michiguni the other day? Did you eat it?
Oh, I ate it. You ate it? It was delicious!
It's delicious! It's so good!
Wow, what's this?
I'm here to advertise.
Why?
It's a cute little memorial.
Oh!
I forgot I told you about this.
It's so sudden.
Yes, "Cute Memorial" is...
It's a song about a girl's wavering feelings when she falls in love.
The lyrics of this song are very straightforward.
It's cheerful.
Yes, sir.
The bright and shiny melody will make you feel like you're in love.
This song is sure to be the background music for your memorial day!
That's a template!
It is also important to note that the phrase "cute" appears a lot!
By all means!
Please check out "Cute Memorial" on music distribution sites and CDs!
That's a template!
And now, we're preparing a variety of videos for the week of the release.
We are preparing various videos for the week of release.
Please look forward to it as well!
I think I'm going to eat one of the axes, too!
Hahaha!
I'm looking forward to the yakiniku bento!We're waiting for your yakiniku bento.
Julia... let's get a raw chopstick.
I'll have the yellow chopsticks.
Just one complete meal!
With a bright and sparkling melody
It's the kind of music that will be the background music for your cute memorial days!
I hope that everyone's daily life will be brightened by the power of cute memorials!
Just now, I heard Oharu's template
She's doing a live broadcast.
I'll show you all.
It looks like we're going to do a live broadcast in a hurry.
I wonder if the fan club members saw it.
What?
Normal is good.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm gonna go ahead and call it a pitch.
That's a good one.
I just did.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
Oh, I can see your back so well.
I'm full of earring-tired people.
Sorry.
I'll ask next time.
This debut.
Gentle.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
To the hearts of Darama,
Darama, we're all very excited.
Please give us your best wishes.
First of all, we will be in Nagoya, Aichi Prefecture.
I'll be there,
The distance of the advertising stunt, maybe 5 cm.
Too close.
I have to be careful.You have to be a little careful.
Like a theme park.
I like it too much Dansky, Dansky, Dansky, Dansky.
I can't help it. Dansky, Dansky, Dansky, Dansky.
So cute, so cute I can't stop, Love Love Love
Sweet Sweet Love Love Love
Thank you for watching.
In case you're wondering, it's just dancing and stuff,
I'm going to fall down in the dance and so on,
Data is just data and dancing, right?
Yes.
And I have already made a lot of them,
So, if you could just ask them to submit all the basic data, that would be fine,
It's normal, you know, to cover the data.
It's the same with the number of people, isn't it?
The number of people, yes, that's right.
And it wasn't names.
Why not?
Aki-chan.
Aki-chan, here.
On something like a small vinyl.
Red vinyl.
You cut this off, didn't you?
Ah...
It doesn't even have to go with everyone else's.
Is it okay if I do that?
I'd love to do that.
Okay, everyone, please come in.
I'm going to let you all have a good night's sleep.
Okay, thank you all very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Today, I would like to thank you all for guiding us on the fourth day.
Yes, thank you very much.Yes, thank you very much.
This venue is really easy to see.
I feel it is very close.
So I'm really looking forward to seeing the audience.
Today, too, we were allowed to charge various kinds of food, so I had some for my pioli.
Um, I think we were doing a live fan club broadcast earlier,
Did you guys, the fan club members, see it?
Let's do our best, let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
We're almost there. Let's do our best. Let's go eat something delicious.
Wow, something's coming.
The chicken wings are here.
Here come the chicken wings.
Wow.
Looks delicious.
It's cute.
Cake cat.
Take a taste of the joint.
This is a delicious way to eat
Hands first
If you split it, you get two? This one.
Oh, is that what you mean?
It's easier to eat, isn't it? No more bones.
How many cat food can I put in the cat food container?
What cat food?
Cheesecake. Cheesecake.
Do you want some in the fridge?
I think we should put some in the fridge.
I'll put some in the fridge.
There's too much stuff in the fridge.
Third one of the day.
It's the third outfit of the day.
I had the second outfit loosened up.
I don't care how much you eatI don't care how much you eat.
Oranges.
Mmm.
Delicious!
This is...
Not bad at all, huh?
Something like this?
Where's the piccoli?
Doala?
Samis?
Doala.
He's very popular, Doala.
This is... Polila.
Polila!
Can you hold it?
Yes, I can.
Give me your hand.
I'm having a baby Pavlin!
I'm having a baby Pavlin.
That's good. That's good.
Take good care of her.
Okay, let's get ready.
Pavlin.
I'll put it back in, baby.
Please, please.
I'm begging you.
Please, please, please, please.
Cute baby!
Baby
Yes, I'll go then. Yes, go ahead.
Today we have the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023.
Cute, cute, too cute! Thank you very much for coming to the "Super Tokimeki Advertising Department Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023.
Please be aware that it is forbidden to disturb other guests. In case of emergency, please follow the instructions of the staff and evacuate the venue.
Please follow the instructions of the staff and evacuate in case of emergency.
As we have already informed you, Aki-chan is unable to sing due to a throat problem, so she will be performing only as a dancer.Aki-chan is unable to sing due to a throat problem, so she will be performing only as a dancer.
But her voice will be heard, so we would be happy if you could join in the fun as if Aki-chan were singing!
Thank you very much.
The show will start soon.
Everyone, we will do our best to have fun!
So, please wait for me! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
mình의 앤k Lebanon
Happy Birthday!
Slippery is better.
It smells so good like that.
Smells so good
I got you.
My hand.
It came through my hand.
I got it.
Five.
Four. - Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Antti!
Yeah!
Kirby! Kirby!
That was amazing! That was close to the best ever!
Let's get excited!
I'm going to give Hiyori an earful today and let him know what I think. I'm sorry.
I can speak in a quiet voice, but not in a loud voice.
Cute. Cute.
So, really,
That's why,
I wanted to say, "That's why I love you, and I can't stop feeling this way.
Ah, I was so excited.Oh, it was so loud.
So I asked if everyone in this venue would like to do "This feeling won't stop from now on,
Aki-chan says.
Will you do it?
I'm going to transforms!
This feeling
I won't stop!
surface 244 000 Harsh
spheres
치료 웃 pięr
Thank you loudly
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming to Nagoya love
[Applause]
We're done. Now, is this on film?
Estagodiver.
Yes, so today was the Nagoya show.
Thank you very much.
I was so excited.
Yes, well, how was everyone?
Hey, what?
I'm talking here.
It was kind of great. You guys delivered a lot of feeling from a great distance.
Everyone was moving so much. It was like the sight of Nagoya.
And the cheering was so loud, it made me so happy.
Everyone was happy.
Were you able to see us?
I'm so happy because Nagoya was also a soul douche.
And there is only one last show left in the tour.
It's early.
When the tour started, we thought we had about 4 months to go.
We said we could go to many places.
Now we have one more show left,
We will be back in June.
I feel like we had another great summer this year.I feel like I had another great summer this year.
It was very fulfilling.
We went to so many places.
We have one show, but let's go and do our best!
I'll do my best!
Also, I would like to come to Nagoya!
I'll be there!
Thank you! See you soon!
Bye bye!
Stability.
Something that's not in the picture.
Like a samurai.
Thank you.
If you liked today's video,
Good button!
It's good, right?
Will you write a comment?
I want it, so please do.
Please comment a lot on Twitter and X.
And watch lots of YouTube!
It's amazing!
Amazing!
Bye bye!
Good job!
I'm half blind.
Isn't this scary?
A little scary.
Oh, there it is!
Too bad you can't see it.
Subscribe to my channel!
I don't know why, but when I laugh.
It's like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy
Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to walkOtherwise, I wouldn't be able to walk.
Somewhere someone is crying
And somewhere you'll get wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future
It's guiding me
Subtitle: Kyou
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
When you're lost, just remember
I'll smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering...
My heart is like a sunny day, I'll let you play with my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Lalala...
Please subscribe to our channel!